Hello friends, welcome to IndianSherTips.com.
Today we are going to bring you a
special topic that will be close to your heart
and we will discuss it in the
context of health plans.
So remember, if you
want to talk to us on any other topic and you want
us to make a video on it, then you can
WhatsApp us on the given number or you
can also look forward
your comments on the video.
So, we have brought for you the best health plans
which will be addressed by the number of parameters, which is the
best plan suits your
pocket also and gives you the best
stability.
Choosing a hospital is important because if you do
not take a health plan, then these
people will take away your life's savings.
Therefore, the sooner you can take a health plan,
the better. So, we have
compared 15 health plans for you and the
helplines of 15 companies and we hope that you will be able to make
a good choice. You can do your further
research on these companies. We have provided
you with a chart in which everything has been
clearly explained to you.
Health plan is the most important
thing, but you have to take it and
you should not hesitate in this that I should save money today
because if you save money today then it is
possible that your entire life's earnings may be
spent in some hospital, so let us first of all
how have we divided this health plan, in this we have given
product rating, which is the
track record rating in followers, how much
time it takes to process the claims, how much
trouble you face in processing it
and keeping these two parameters in mind, the
overall rating has been given and lastly,
how friendly it will be on your pocket, that
premium affordability rating has been
given according to the money, so
if we look at these product ratings, at present APO Platinum
Health Plan has got number five out of five,
in claim record it has
4.3,
its overall rating is 4.9 and it is also pocket
friendly, here in pocket
friendly, see that where the number is
bigger, like here it is five, then
it means that this is a costly plan, so
compare to the plan with number three, then once  Let's
repeat the product
rating, plans, track record,
overall rating. And then finally, you have to
compare it with the money value, whether this
plan suits you or not.
I'll rub this out, show date, you can have an
look at the chart properly. So, first of all,
you have to see if any
plan
suits your overall rating. If you do, then
you have to buy it. You
also have to look at your pocket. Apart from this, we will see two more things:
if that company
lives for the next 35-40 years, will that company
remain in existence or not? According to us,
HDFC will remain in existence, ICC will also
remain in existence, Reliance will also
remain in existence.
Rest of the companies are partnership companies. It is
difficult to comment on them
because many of their partners
are overseas partners and it becomes difficult to comment on their state of affairs.
At least they can be the share of the
company which is listed in India. So,
these are the brands which may be listed. It is
possible that many companies have tyres
from foreign companies and they are very big
insurance companies.  There may be companies in the sector, but in life,
we would prefer to
go with brands that are listed in India,
which we can monitor. It shouldn't happen
that we buy a plan and
then it fails. So,
look at HDFC Ego, it also has a good
rating of 4.9, its track record is also
good at 4.7, its track record is better and its
overall rating is 4.8,
and it is also a little expensive on the pocket. Next,
compare it with APO, then
look at ICC Lombard, its claim
track record is good, it also has an
overall rating of 4.8, and it is also pocket-
friendly. So, if you look at these things,
you can compare all these plans
and see that Neem Bhupa is also a good company,
Star Health is also a good company, and it is the
most expensive on your pocket.
If you look at these things, it is the most expensive on your pocket.
Aditya Birla Group's
premium is the most expensive on your pocket. So, keeping these
things in mind, you
can decide which company's plan you should buy.
We have listed the chart for you, let's print it
out, so you can check it.
Take the correct decision on the plan
which is to be taken by you.
We hope you have understood the details of these companies.
Most insurance companies will
suggest health plans to you.
They may earn higher commissions there, but you should
also do your own research. So, date you are not
taken on a right.
Now, it remains to be seen who needs to
take this health plan.
Now, many central or state government
employees will say, "We already have a
health plan, so why do we need to take it?" This is
true, but if you are going to retire, then
take it some time before that
so that your premium is reduced and it works as a
backup. For example, the Central
Government will have the CST scheme or the
Paramilitary Army, Air Force, Navy or
X-K.
These schemes may
not have the facilities that are available in them. For example, if
you take many insurance plans,
Ayurveda treatments are also available in them,
which you can avail under the insurance plan.
Recently, some updates have come
that Ayurveda is also included in the Central Government Health Scheme and
X-K etc.  Treatments are being provided to
these corporates but whether they will
provide it to you or not is not
known at that time, so you should take a small plane as a backup,
even if you take a small plane worth five lakhs. It
is necessary for private employees to
take a health insurance plan
because the company provides it to them but it is
possible that their families are
not included in it, so they can talk to the company people and by
paying extra premium, they can include their
family members also under the health insurance
plan and
the sooner you take the health insurance plan, the
lesser the premium you will have to pay
for life because as you grow
old, the premium of the plan will
increase and
after a particular stage, it is possible
that you may not get the insurance plan because
you may have some existing disease.
Self-employed, without any doubt, this person should
always take the health plan first
because a self-employed person works the
most because he himself drinks the liquor of his company, he himself is the
runner, he himself is the tea
seller, everything, so he has the maximum stress, so
he has to worry about his health.
And it is important to maintain the health of your family,
so health insurance is great,
otherwise remember that the white collar workers will take away all your
money and lastly those who are about to
retire are going on RS, so
they have to take insurance plan on time
because the money you invest in it will
come to this level at some point or the other. If you feel that
you have to give all the money to the doctor,
then the insurance company
steps in and you are facing the danger
of losing all your money, so do
n't think that insurance is
your money which will be lost because if you want to
recover it, then you will have to be insured for that. It is
better that this money is lost,
that is fine, but
you get benefit in your future premium also
if you have not made a claim. So take
good care of your health and
if you liked it, then do not forget to like, share and subscribe
and we will keep bringing more good videos for you.
Our
best plan in intraday is Bank Nifty option,
use it,
you just have to
give time up to ₹915M,
use capital of 10000  And you
can earn up to 30% intraday profit.
Any trade is always done
with a stop loss. Stop loss is not
your enemy but a friend because it is your
risk control mechanism.
You don't have time in the morning, so make it work on
Nifty option tips.
Nifty option is generally given in the afternoon session.
Data formation is taken place,
it is based on the data analytics and in that
we generally give it to you in the afternoon session
and its reliability and accuracy is
good and better to a great extent and
you can make good returns with less capital.
In this also you can start with a capital of Rs 10,000. If you have
any query, you
can call us tomorrow or WhatsApp us and
we will hand over to you.
Our success is in your success. Thank you.